

LE VAN HUNG

Java Developer

Personal Details

20/03/2001



0355 01 25 25



vanhung.work@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/lvhungg/





Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh City



Male

Career Objective

I'm a senior majoring in Software Engineering. With a dynamic, inquisitive, hardworking personality, I look forward to working as a Java Developer at your company. I will try to complete the assigned tasks well, learn more professional experience, constantly striving to achieve management positions within the next 3 years.

Skills

Programming:

Know and use basic programming languages: HTML, CSS, .NET MVC, PHP, Java, C#.

Teamwork:

Regularly assigned to the position of team leader, therefore experienced in team management.

Education

VAN LANG UNIVERSITY | 08/2019 - NOW Software Engineering

GPA: 3.43/4.0

Work Experience

- Van Lang University | 02/2021 06/2021

 Teaching Assistant for Information system application Database.
 - Supporting instructors to teach subjects.
 - Grading student assignments.
 - Answer questions for more than 100 students on subject-related issues.
- Van Lang University | 12/2021 03/2022

 Teaching Assistant for Object Oriented Programming and C#
 - Support lecturers to teach subjects.
 - Guide students to code some simple functions.
 - Answer questions for more than 50 students on subject-related issues.
- Van Lang University | 01/2022 04/2022 Admission Counseling Collaborator

Join the school's admission counseling team to share knowledge about the school to students in high schools in Ho Chi Minh City and the knowledge of the current major being studied.

Activities

GREEN SUMMER VOLUNTEER CAMPAIGN 2019 | 05/2019 - 07/2019

Volunteer

Responsible for the communication of the campaign, thereby bringing this volunteer campaign to everyone, especially students.

ITSM TRADITIONAL FESTIVAL | 08/2020 - 11/2020
Members of The Organizing Committee

The positions of artist managers who will make the concert more successful.

STUDENT SPORTS FESTIVAL | 03/2022 - 05/2022

Delegation Leader

The delegation leader, supporting the schedule as well as cheering the spirit for students.

Achievements

Other Soft Skills:

Make good use of skills: presentation skill, communicating with strangers, problem solving.

Foreign Language:

Listening, speaking, reading, writing at a normal level.

Interests

- Read technology news.
- Experience new applications and software.

2019 - 2020: Excellent Volunteer - Organized by HoChiMinh Communist Youth Union of Vang Lang University.

2020: Warrior against Corona - Organized by HoChiMinh Communist Youth Union of Vang Lang University.

2019 - 2022: Excellent Student for 5 consecutive semesters - Faculty of Information Technology - Van Lang University.

2021 - 2022: Outstanding Student - Van Lang University.

2021: Third prize of VIETNAM DEV CHALLENGE - VLU's Job Fair 2021 organized by TopCV.

Certificate

2021: Teaching Assistant Certificate granted by Van Lang University.

2021: HMS Foundation Course granted by Huawei.